WHAT'S GOING ON?
HUH? WELL, MY EYE
IS A LITTLE ITCHY.
UH... MINE, TOO. YEAH.
WOW, IT'S REALLY RED.
YOU SHOULD GO SEE
MY EYE DOCTOR.
RICHARD? I'M NOT GOING TO
GO SEE YOUR EX-BOYFRIEND.
RICHARD--
THAT'S ALL I EVER HEAR.
RICHARD, RICHARD, RICHARD.
SINCE WE'VE BEEN GOING OUT
I THINK I'VE MENTIONED
HIS NAME TWICE.
OKAY, SO RICHARD, RICHARD.
IT'S NOT RICHARD, OKAY?
IT'S THIS NEW GUY,
AND HE'S REALLY GOOD.
WELL, I'M SORRY,
I'M NOT GOING TO AN EYE DOCTOR.
OH, GOD, HERE WE GO.
Chandler:
WHAT?
ANYTIME ANYTHING COMES
CLOSE TO TOUCHING HER EYE
OR ANYONE ELSE'S,
SHE, LIKE, FREAKS OUT.
WATCH. WATCH.
ROSS! COME ON. THAT'S...
ALL RIGHT, FINE, OKAY
I HAVE A WEIRD THING
WITH MY EYE.
CAN WE JUST NOT TALK
ABOUT IT, PLEASE?
All:
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, RACHE, YOU KNOW
THAT GREAT SONG
UM, "ME, MYSELF AND... EYE"?
AAH! MONICA! COME ON.
HEY, DOES ANYONE WANT
TO GET SOME LUNCH?
ALL THOSE IN FAVOR, SAY "EYE."
ROSS! STOP IT! COME ON.
HOW MUCH DID I LOVE
THE KING AND EYE?
CHANDLER. ALL RIGHT...
ME, TOO! ME, TOO! ME, TOO!
ALL RIGHT,
JUST STOP IT!
THAT'S ENOUGH!
COME ON.
YOU OKAY THERE, MAN?
YEAH. I GOT TOO EXCITED.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
ALL RIGHT,
I GOT TO GO.
I'M TAKING BEN
TO THE PARK.
OH, GIVE HIM A KISS FOR ME.
ALL RIGHT. BYE.
BYE.
LATER.
( laughing )
I AM SO SORRY YOU GOT CAUGHT
IN THE MIDDLE OF THAT.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO BE SO OUT THERE
BUT I AM FURIOUS WITH HIM.
WOW. UM...
CALM DOWN?
I'M TRYING, BUT, MAN,
THAT GUY CAN PUSH MY BUTTONS.
WHY ARE YOU SO MAD AT HIM?
LOOK, I DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT, OKAY?
IT JUST SEEMS...
YOU WANT TO BE ON
MY LIST, TOO? KEEP TALKING.
HAS ANYONE SEEN MY LIST,
BY THE WAY?
UH, NO, PHEEBS.
WHAT'S IT LOOK LIKE?
IT'S A PIECE OF PAPER,
AND IT SAYS "ROSS" ON IT.
I SEE.
HI.
HEY.
I JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH ESTELLE, AND GUESS WHAT?
I GOT THE LEAD IN A MOVIE!
CONGRATULATIONS!
THAT'S AMAZING.
WHAT'S THE
MOVIE ABOUT?
OH, UH,
IT'S CALLED SHUTTER SPEED.
IT'S REALLY COOL. YEAH.
UM, WELL, I MEET THIS GIRL
ON THE SUBWAY
AND WE FALL IN LOVE
IN, LIKE, A DAY, RIGHT?
AND THEN, SHE DISAPPEARS
BUT I FIND OUT WHERE SHE LIVES,
AND WHEN I GET THERE
THIS, LIKE, OLD LADY
ANSWERS THE DOOR
AND I SAY, "WHERE'S BETSY?"
RIGHT? AND SHE SAYS, "BETSY'S
BEEN DEAD FOR TEN YEARS."
OOH... CHILLING.
YEAH.
OH, AND THE BEST PART IS
WE'RE FILMING IN THE DESERT
OUTSIDE OF VEGAS.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT
MEANS, BUDDY?
I KNOW WHAT THAT
MEANS, BUDDY.
ROAD TRIP! YEAH.
WE CAN RENT A CAR.
I JUST HAVE TO BE THERE
BY TUESDAY.
OOH, WAIT,
MY GRANDMOTHER'S DEAD.
WELL, UH... WE CAN TALK
ABOUT THAT, TOO, PHEEBS.
NO, NO.
HER CAB--
SHE PROBABLY WON'T BE USING IT.
YOU COULD DRIVE IT TO LAS VEGAS.
ALL RIGHT! THANKS, PHEEBS.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO
ABOUT MY JOB?
OH, UH, NOT GO.
ALL RIGHT! GREAT!
ROAD TRIP, BABY!
( chortling )
IS THIS OKAY WITH YOU?
CHANDLER, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO ASK FOR MY PERMISSION.
YOU CAN GO.
THANK YOU.
HEY, RACHE, COME ON.
YOU'LL BE LATE
FOR THE EYE DOCTOR APPOINTMENT.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET THIS OVER WITH.
( groans )
OH... NO.
LOOK WHAT I DID.
OH...
I MEAN, LOOK AT THIS MESS.
I MEAN, WE'RE GOING TO PROBABLY
HAVE TO CLEAN THIS UP, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO RESCHEDULE.
IF YOU THOUGHT THAT THIS MESS
WAS GOING TO BOTHER ME
YOU ARE WRONG.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GO, BLINKY.
ALL RIGHT.
( Rachel groans in frustration)
CHANDLER...
OH, HEY, JOEY.
HEY.
WHAT'S UP?
WELL, I CAN'T DECIDE
WHICH ROUTE TO TAKE TO VEGAS.
HEY... YOU'VE TRAVELED
A LOT, RIGHT?
YEAH, I'VE BEEN AROUND.
OKAY...
SO... SO WHICH ROUTE
SHOULD I TAKE
THE NORTHERN ROUTE
OR THE SOUTHERN ROUTE?
OOH, IF YOU TAKE
THE NORTHERN ROUTE
THERE'S A MAN IN ILLINOIS
WITH A BEARD OF BEES.
( gasps )
GREAT! PROBLEM SOLVED.
BUT ON THE SOUTHERN ROUTE
THERE'S A CHICKEN THAT
PLAYS TIC-TAC-TOE.
WELL, BACK TO SQUARE ONE.
OH, I KNOW A WAY
THAT YOU CAN DECIDE.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO ASK
YOU A SERIES OF QUESTIONS
AND YOU ANSWER AS
QUICKLY AS YOU CAN.
( quickly ):
YES.
GOOD, BUT WAIT.
OKAY... ALL RIGHT
HERE WE GO. NOW, I
WANT YOU TO RELAX...
TAKE A DEEP BREATH,
CLEAR YOUR MIND...
WHICH DO YOU
LIKE BETTER
PEANUT BUTTER
OR EGG WHITES?
PEANUT BUTTER.
WOULD YOU RATHER BE A
FIREMAN OR A SWIMMER?
A SWIMMER.
WOULD YOU RATHER SLEEP
WITH MONICA OR RACHEL?
MONICA. OH...
HUH. I ALWAYS THOUGHT
IT'D BE RACHEL.
NO THINKING, NO THINKING.
TIE OR ASCOT?
ASCOT.
NORTH ROUTE OR
SOUTH ROUTE?
NORTH ROUTE.
BAM! THERE YOU GO, HUH?
WOW.
THAT WAS INCREDIBLE.
BEARD OF BEES, HERE I COME.
HEY.
OH, THIS GUY AGAIN.
HEY, MAN,
WHAT'S UP?
UH, NOT MUCH.
YOU GUYS WANT TO SEE
A MOVIE TONIGHT?
SURE, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO SEE?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW. UM...
I KNOW HOW WE CAN DECIDE.
PHOEBE, SHOW HIM YOUR GAME.
UM, NO THANK YOU.
WHAT'S WITH HER?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT, HEY, I KNOW
HOW WE CAN DECIDE.
OKAY, I'M GOING
TO ASK YOU QUESTIONS
AND YOU ANSWER
REAL QUICK, OKAY?
OKAY.
ACTION OR COMEDY?
ACTION.
WHO WOULD YOU RATHER SLEEP WITH,
MONICA OR RACHEL?
DUDE, YOU ARE SICK.
OH, RIGHT, I'M SORRY.
I FORGOT YOU HAD
THAT WHOLE RACHEL THING.
I'M SORRY.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT DOES THAT THING DO?
HMM, IT'S AN EYE
REMOVAL MACHINE.
ALL RIGHT, I'M OUT OF HERE.
I'M KIDDING, I'M KIDDING.
UH-OH.
HI, RACHEL.
HEY.
I'M DR. MILLER.
MONICA TOLD ME
YOU WERE A LITTLE NERVOUS
BUT EVERYTHING'S
GOING TO BE JUST FINE.
SO, WE'RE DONE THEN.
ALMOST-- FIRST
WE GOT TO START.
OKAY.
THIS IS THE GLAUCOMA TEST.
UH-HUH.
SIT DOWN.
OKAY.
PUT YOUR CHIN HERE.
MM-HMM.
NOW, YOU'RE
GOING TO FEEL
A SMALL PUFF OF
AIR IN EACH EYE.
W-WH-WHAT?
A SMALL PUFF OF AIR.
( sharply ):
NOW, COME ON!
HERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
OKAY, I'M SORRY.
ALL RIGHT, JUST...
I'M STAYING HERE THIS TIME.
OKAY.
READY?
UH-HUH.
ONE, TWO, TH...
I'M SORRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO
HOLD HER HEAD.
THAT'S OKAY.
OKAY.
ONE...
UH-HUH.
TWO...
I'M SORRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE YOUNG
YOU PROBABLY DON'T
HAVE GLAUCOMA.
( cheering )
OKAY, SO...
IT'S WAS VERY,
VERY NICE TO MEET YOU.
OH, HEY... WHAT, ARE YOU CRAZY?
OKAY, YOU HAVE A SMALL,
MINOR INFECTION
IN THAT LEFT EYE.
I WANT YOU TO
TAKE THESE DROPS
THREE TIMES A
DAY FOR A WEEK
AND YOU'LL BE
AS GOOD AS NEW.
NO, I DON'T PUT THINGS
IN MY EYE.
OKAY, THEN, I GUESS
WE'LL SEE YOU
BACK HERE IN
THREE MONTHS.
GREAT.
AND I'LL FIT YOU
FOR A GLASS EYE.
OKAY, JUST GIVE ME
THE DAMN DROPS.
DR. MILLER...
P-E-C-F-D.
VERY GOOD, MONICA.
YOU KNOW WHERE THEY ARE.
I SURE DO.
AND YOU DON'T GET ONE.
YOU KNOW,
I GOT TO TELL YOU
THOSE EYE DROPS
ARE A MIRACLE
MY EYE IS
100 PERCENT BETTER.
THEY'RE STILL IN MY COAT.
DAMN.
HEY.
HEY, YOU READY TO GO?
YEAH. HOW COLD IS IT
GOING TO BE?
DO I NEED A COAT OR WILL ALL
THESE SWEATER-VESTS BE ENOUGH.
WHAT?
I LOVE YOU.
MAN, I WISH ROSS
WAS COMING WITH US, YOU KNOW.
I'M GOING TO MISS HIM.
THANKS A LOT.
I JUST GOT THAT JERK
OUT OF MY MIND.
HEY, SO WHERE ARE WE STAYING?
IS THE MOVIE PUTTING US UP
IN A BIG HOTEL SUITE?
AH, NO,
NOT REALLY.
IT'S AN INDEPENDENT FILM
SO WE DON'T HAVE
A REAL BIG BUDGET.
I FIGURED I'D JUST STAY
IN YOUR ROOM.
I SEE, BUT ONCE YOU GET
YOUR FIRST PAYCHECK
YOU'LL BE SPRINGING FOR A BIG
HOTEL SUITE, RIGHT?
I MEAN LEAD IN A MOVIE
THEY MUST BE
PAYING YOU A LOT.
OH, YEAH, CHECK THIS OUT--
FOR EVERY DOLLAR
SHUTTER SPEED MAKES
ONE PENNY OF IT GOES
RIGHT IN JOEY'S POCKET.
SO YOU DON'T GET PAID
UNLESS THE MOVIE
MAKES MONEY?
DID YOU NOT HEAR
THE PLOT OF THE MOVIE?
SHE'S BEEN DEAD
FOR TEN YEARS.
I'M GOING TO BE
A MILLIONAIRE!
HEY.
JUST WANTED TO SAY GOOD-BYE
TO YOU GUYS
AND TO SEE IF MAYBE YOU GUYS
WILL PLACE A LITTLE BET
FOR ME, HUH?
20 BUCKS ON BLACK 15.
YOU GOT IT.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, BYE-BYE NOW.
BYE, YOU GUYS.
BYE.
I'LL SAY GOOD-BYE
AT THE CAR.
OKAY.
OH, ANYBODY WANT TO SAY
GOOD-BYE TO ME AT THE CAR?
OH, HONEY, I'LL SAY GOOD-BYE
TO YOU AT THE CAR
IF YOU DON'T MIND THE PUS.
SEE YA.
NO, WAIT A MINUTE.
THE PUS IS GOOD.
IT MEANS IT'S HEALING.
HEY, PHEEBS,
WHATCHA READING?
PHEEBS?
HELLO.
PHOEBE?
PHEE... PHEE... PHOEBE.
PHOEBE, COME ON.
OH, I'M SORRY, I
DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE.
PHEEBS, ARE YOU MAD AT ME
OR SOMETHING?
'CAUSE IF YOU ARE
PLEASE TELL ME
WHAT IT IS I DID.
WELL, IF YOU DON'T KNOW,
I CAN'T HELP YOU.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, I CAN'T HELP YOU.
OKAY, WELL, WHATEVER IT IS
I AM VERY, VERY SORRY, OKAY?
APOLOGY ACCEPTED.
OKAY.
SO, WE'RE GOOD?
UH-HUH.
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER, OKAY?
BYE, FAT ASS.
ALL RIGHT.
PHOEBE, NOW COME ON
WOULD YOU PLEASE TELL ME
WHAT IT IS
THAT MADE YOU SO MAD AT ME.
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T REMEMBER.
WELL, IF YOU CAN'T REMEMBER
CAN'T WE JUST FORGET ABOUT THIS?
OH, NO, I AM MAD AT YOU
I KNOW THAT MUCH.
BUT I AM SORRY
ABOUT THE FAT ASS THING
'CAUSE YOU ACTUALLY HAVE
A VERY SWEET LITTLE HEINIE.
MAN, I'M GETTING
PRETTY TIRED.
YOU MIGHT HAVE
TO TAKE OVER SOON.
WE'VE BEEN DRIVING
FOR A HALF HOUR.
AND YOU HAVEN'T LOOKED
AT THE ROAD ONCE.
DON'T WORRY, IT'S OUT THERE.
MAYBE I JUST
NEED LUNCH.
YEAH.
YOU WANT TO EAT?
MY TREAT.
ISN'T THAT ROSS'S
MONEY?
YEAH, OKAY,
ROSS'S TREAT.
WHERE DO YOU
WANT TO EAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
OH, HEY
I KNOW HOW WE CAN DECIDE.
I'M GOING TO ASK YOU
A BUNCH OF QUESTIONS
AND THEN YOU HAVE TO
ANSWER REAL FAST, OKAY?
SO, CLEAR YOUR MIND.
CLEAR IT RIGHT OUT.
CLEAR IT OUT. CLEAR.
OKAY.
OKAY, WOULD YOU RATHER
BE TOO WET OR TOO DRY?
TOO DRY.
DO YOU BELIEVE IN GHOSTS?
NO.
IS THE MOVIE MY BIG BREAK?
WHAT?
YES.
DUDE, YOU SAID NO.
WELL, I ALSO
SAID YES.
WELL, YOU DON'T THINK
THIS IS GOING TO BE
A BIG BREAK FOR ME?
NO...
( choking )
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
LOOK, JOE, I JUST...
I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO GET YOUR HOPES UP
TOO HIGH, YOU KNOW?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M THE LEAD IN A MOVIE.
THEY'RE NOT EVEN PAYING YOU.
THIS DOESN'T EVEN SOUND
LIKE A REAL MOVIE.
I DON'T NEED THIS.
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU'RE DUMPING
ON MY BIG BREAK.
'CAUSE, JOE, I DON'T THINK THIS
IS GOING TO BE YOUR BIG BREAK.
IS THAT WHY YOU'RE
ON THIS TRIP, HUH?
TO MAKE ME FEEL
LIKE A LOSER?
'CAUSE IF IT IS,
I'D RATHER BE ALONE.
YOU DON'T WANT ME HERE?
NOT IF YOU'RE GOING
TO BE LIKE THIS.
TELL YOU WHAT--
THE NEXT TIME YOU ASK ME
A QUESTION LIKE THAT,
I'LL LIE.
YEAH, I DON'T WANT YOU
ON THE TRIP.
ALL RIGHT, FINE, FINE.
WHY DON'T YOU PULL OVER,
I'LL GET OUT RIGHT NOW.
FINE.
GET OUT.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO STOP ON A BRIDGE.
GET OUT!
ALL RIGHT!
Chandler:
WAIT! WAIT!
THERE'S NO SIDEWALK!
YEAH, I'M GONNA DIE HERE.
ARE YOU MAD AT ME
BECAUSE MY HAIR GEL SMELLS?
Phoebe:
NO.
ARE YOU ANGRY WITH ME
BECAUSE I SAID
YOUR HANDWRITING
IS CHILDLIKE?
NO, THAT MADE ME FEEL PRECIOUS.
OH, I KNOW.
UM, IS IT BECAUSE HE'S ALWAYS
CORRECTING PEOPLE'S GRAMMAR?
"WHOM, WHOM."
SOMETIMES IT'S "WHO."
YEAH, SOMETIMES IT'S...
OH, DID YOU BEAT HIM
AT A BOARD GAME?
HE TURNS INTO
SUCH A BABY WHEN
HE STARTS TO LOSE.
OH, YEAH, I'M THE BABY.
HEY, STOP IT!
HEY.
CHANDLER, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
JOEY KICKED ME OUT
OF THE CAR
ON THE GEORGE WASHINGTON
BRIDGE.
All:
WHY?
HE WENT CRAZY.
WE WERE PLAYING THAT GAME
WHERE YOU ASK A QUESTION
AND YOU HAVE
TO ANSWER REALLY FAST.
OH, THAT GAME SHOULD NOT BE
PLAYED WITHOUT MY SUPERVISION.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
MADE HIM SO MAD.
ALL I SAID WAS THAT
I DIDN'T THINK
THIS WAS GOING TO BE
HIS BIG BREAK.
THAT THIS MOVIE WASN'T
GOING TO DO ANYTHING FOR HIM
AND THAT IT DIDN'T SOUND
LIKE A REAL MOVIE.
OKAY, HE SHOULD HAVE
PUSHED ME OFF THE BRIDGE.
WHAT'S IN THE BAG?
OH, I FIGURED YOU GUYS
WOULD ALL BE MAD AT ME
SO I GOT YOU SOME GIFTS
THAT I FOUND ON THE
SIDE OF THE ROAD.
WHO WANTS THE TEDDY BEAR
WITH ONE LEG?
I DO.
OKAY...
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
OKAY, THEN HELP ME.
I NEED HELP.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
OKAY, COME ON,
LET'S DO IT.
ALL RIGHT.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, PUT
YOUR HEAD BACK.
YES.
ALL RIGHT,
NOW OPEN YOUR EYES.
OKAY, THEY ARE.
HOW MANY FINGERS
AM I HOLDING UP?
FOUR.
OH, MY GOD, I WAS
THINKING FOUR.
REALLY?
YES!
YOU KNOW WHAT? WHY DON'T WE
START WITH A PRACTICE ONE, OKAY?
NO DROPS.
GREAT.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT,
ON THREE.
ONE... TWO... THREE.
MY PILLOW'S ALL WET.
WELL, YOU SAID IT WAS PRACTICE.
THEN WHY DID YOU MOVE?
BECAUSE I KNEW YOU WERE LYING.
ALL RIGHT, COME HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GET... JUST GET...
MONICA, STOP IT!
OH, MY GOD!
STOP IT!
I AM GOING...
TURN IT OVER!
NO!
I AM... I AM GOING
TO GET...
GET THESE DROPS
IN YOUR EYES.
OH, MY GOD!
YOU REALLY ARE
FREAKISHLY STRONG.
( screaming )
MONICA, STOP IT!
( coughs )
DAMN, IT'S EMPTY!
WELL, IF JOEY AND CHANDLER
WALKED IN RIGHT NOW
WE COULD MAKE A FORTUNE.
( phone ringing )
OH, THAT IS DEFINITELY
CHANDLER, JOEY OR ROSS...
OR RACHEL.
HELLO.
IT'S JOEY.
I'M SO GLAD
YOU CALLED.
CHANDLER TOLD ME WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU KNOW, HE'S REALLY
UPSET ABOUT IT.
NOT AS UPSET AS HE'S GOING TO BE
WHEN HE FINDS OUT WHAT I DID
WITH HIS SWEATER-VESTS.
WHAT DID YOU DO
TO HIS SWEATER-VESTS?
LET'S JUST SAY THERE'S
A WELL-DRESSED PACK OF DOGS
IN OHIO.
Hey, Monica, is Phoebe there?
I'VE GOT TO ASK HER SOMETHING
ABOUT THE CAR.
Yeah, she's here.
Hold on one second.
HEY, DUDE.
Hey, Pheebs.
THIS BOX KEEPS SLIDING OUT
FROM UNDER THE SEAT.
WHAT IS IT?
OH, THAT'S MY GRANDMA.
AND THANKS, JOEY.
SHE'S HAVING
A REALLY GREAT TIME.
IS THAT JOEY?
LET ME TALK TO HIM.
OKAY, JOEY, CHANDLER'S HERE.
HE WAS WONDERING IF...
( line disconnects )
OKAY, I GUESS HE RAN OUT
OF CHANGE.
YOU KNOW, HE WON'T
EVEN TALK TO ME.
HOW AM I GOING
TO APOLOGIZE TO HIM
IF HE WON'T EVEN
TALK TO ME?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
SEND HIM SOMETHING.
SO WHEN HE GETS TO LAS VEGAS
HE'LL KNOW THAT YOU'RE SORRY.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
I WONDER WHERE I COULD
GET A BASKET OF PORN?
OH, NO, NO, DON'T SAY I'M SORRY
WITH PORN.
NO?
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU SHOULD SEND HIM--
A CARTON OF CIGARETTES.
'CAUSE THAT WAY HE CAN TRADE IT
FOR PROTECTION...
NO, THAT'S PRISON.
( door opening )
OKAY, PHEEBS, I KNOW HOW
WE'RE GOING TO FIGURE THIS OUT.
OKAY, CLEAR YOUR MIND
AND ANSWER THE FIRST THING
THAT COMES INTO YOUR HEAD, OKAY?
MM-HMM.
WHAT DO YOU LIKE BETTER,
FLORA OR FAUNA?
FAUNA.
SIMON OR GARFUNKLE?
GARFUNKLE.
WHY ARE YOU MAD AT ME?
YOU SAID I WAS BORING. OH!
WHEN DID I SAY
YOU WERE BORING?
OH, MY GOD! I REMEMBER NOW!
WE WERE PLAYING CHESS.
PHOEBE, YOU AND I HAVE
NEVER PLAYED CHESS.
OH, COME ON, YES.
REMEMBER THAT TIME
ON THE FROZEN LAKE
WE WERE PLAYING CHESS.
YOU SAID I WAS BORING
AND THEN YOU TOOK OFF
YOUR ENERGY MASK
AND YOU WERE CAMERON DIAZ.
OKAY, THERE'S A CHANCE
THIS MAY HAVE BEEN A DREAM.
HEY.
STANLEY!
HEY-HEY!
YOUR LEADING MAN IS HERE.
LET'S GET TO WORK.
UM, SLIGHT
CHANGE OF PLANS.
WE'VE SHUT DOWN.
WHA... WHAT?
WHY?
IT'S A MONEY THING.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY.
( chuckling )
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
NO.
WHAT?
IT'S PROBABLY
JUST TEMPORARY.
WE'RE HOPING TO GET
SOME MORE MONEY SOON.
SO IF YOU COULD
JUST HANG OUT.
HANG OUT?
HOW LONG?
I DON'T KNOW,
A WEEK, MAYBE TWO.
THE MONEY WILL
TURN UP.
PEOPLE ALWAYS WANT
TO INVEST IN MOVIES.
HEY, YOU'RE NOT RICH, ARE YOU?
NO.
WORTH A SHOT.
LOOK, JOEY, LET ME KNOW
WHERE YOU'RE STAYING, OKAY?
HEY, PAL.
ARE YOU JOEY TRIBBIANI?
YEAH.
THESE GOT
LEFT FOR YOU.
THANKS.
"CONGRATULATIONS
ON YOUR BIG BREAK."
( phone ringing )
HELLO.
Hey, Monica, it's Joey.
HEY, JOEY.
OH, YOU REMEMBER ME EVEN THOUGH
YOU'RE A BIG STAR.
Oh, come on.
It'll be years
before I forget you.
JOEY, WHAT'S IT LIKE
ON A MOVIE SET, HUH?
DO YOU HAVE A DRESSING ROOM?
DO YOU HAVE A CHAIR
WITH YOUR NAME ON IT?
Yeah, yeah, I got all that
going on, yeah.
Listen, I want you to make sure
you tell Chandler
that he couldn't have
been more wrong.
Uh-oh, I got to go, Monica.
My... my sushi's here.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
THANKS FOR WAITING.
OKAY.
EVERYBODY SMILE.
THANKS A LOT.
ENJOY YOUR STAY AT CAESARS.
WE HOPE IT'S TOGA-RIFFIC.
KILL ME. KILL ME NOW.
RACHE, CAN YOU PASS
ME THE TV GUIDE?
YEAH.
GO!
WHAT?!
GET AWAY!
OH, MY GOD!
Monica:
HOLD HER. OKAY.
WE'LL SEE YOU IN ABOUT
THREE OR FOUR HOURS.
AW.